

# **NURULHUDA**

T: +6013-4450 067 E: Nurhuda5444@yahoo.com

Administrative

#### PROFILE

Full Name: Nurulhuda Binti Mohd Zulkifli

**Age:** 25

Nationality: Malaysian

Address: No. 4, Jalan Solok Segar

Taman Lim

30100 Ipoh, Perak.

Service-focused, technically skilled and hardworking office support professional with one and half years of experience as a sales assistant. Advanced skills in MS Office Suite (Word, Excel, Access, PowerPoint and Outlook); demonstrated ability to learn new computer programs quickly.

### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Ms Office	5	0
Ms Project	5	0
Filing & Record	5	0
Teamwork	5	0
Management	5	0
Windows	5	0
Communication	5	0
Administrative	5	0

## TANGUAGES

Malay		50
English		50

### FOLLOW ME



More info on: Nurulhuda

### WORK EXPERIENCE

08<sup>th</sup> August 2016 - 25<sup>th</sup> November 2016.

INTERNSHIP- @SILVERSTONE BERHAD., KAMUNTING, PERAK
Responsible for daily defect of summary report, daily
summary of uniformity results, defect List/ SSM Inspection
Standard, RFV Graph Marking, documentation of tire
specification, return spec and SM chart, attendance and
leave documentation in Technical Service department.

02<sup>nd</sup> December 2013 - 27<sup>th</sup> February 2015.

SALES ASSISTANT - @PSE INDUSTRIAL SUPPLIES SDN BHD

Serving as a sales assistant, selling and promoting goods spare parts of various brands of quality, answer telephones and transfer to appropriate staff member, make receipts and photocopy work, meet and greet clients and visitors, create and modify documents using Microsoft Office, perform general clerical duties to include but not limited to: photocopying, faxing, mailing, and filing. Maintain hard copy and electronic filing system, research, price, and purchase office furniture and supplies, coordinate and maintain records for staff office space, phones, staff leaves, and staff attendance. Setup and coordinate meetings and conferences, maintain and distribute staff weekly schedules, collect and maintain PC inventory, support staff in assigned project based work, provide office orientation for new employees, and other duties as assigned.

16<sup>th</sup> June 2013- 29<sup>th</sup> November 2013.

SALES ASSISTANT - @HLK VENTURES SDN BHD

Duty to as a sales clerk, selling and promoting shop lots and offices in Pasir Puteh Central which is still under construction, answer telephones and transfer to appropriate staff member, meet and greet clients and visitors, create and modify documents using Microsoft Office, perform general clerical duties to include but not limited to: photocopying, faxing, mailing, and filing.

# EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS
ADMINISTRATION WITH HONOURS
(OPERATIONS MANAGEMENT)

DIPLOMA IN BUSINESS STUDIES

UiTM Merbok, Kedah

F 0017

Merbok, Kedah

2015-2017

2010-2013

II TM

#### REFERENCES

DR JAMALUDIN BIN AKBAR

Senior Lecturer, Faculty of Business & Management Universiti Teknologi MARA (UiTM) Cawangan Kedah.

Tel: 04-4562185 (O) 013-4274729 (HP)

Email:

jamal691@kedah.uitm.edu.my

SITI FAIRUZA BINTI HASSAM

Senior Lecturer, Faculty of Business & Management Universiti Teknologi MARA (UiTM) Cawangan Kedah.

Tel: 04-4562170 (O) 019-6425853 (HP)

Email: fairuza@kedah.uitm.edu.my